A Guide to the Downtown-Lower Manhattan Association, Inc. records FA085
Rockefeller Archive Center
- DLMA, Inc., 1957-1995; 2; 78.875 Cubic Feet 214 document cases
  - Projects, 1957-1995; 2.3; 42.125 Cubic Feet 121 document cases
    - New York Chamber of Commerce and Industry, September-December 1979 (Box 138, Folder 1385)
    - New York Chamber of Commerce and Industry, 1980-1981 (Box 138, Folder 1386)
    - New York Chamber of Commerce and Industry, 1982 (Box 138, Folder 1387)
    - New York Chamber of Commerce and Industry, 1983-1984 (Box 139, Folder 1388)
    - New York Chamber of Commerce and Industry, 1985-1987 (Box 139, Folder 1389)
    - New York Chamber of Commerce and Industry, 1988-1990 (Box 139, Folder 1390)
    - New York Chamber of Commerce and Industry - The Borough Relations Committee - Economic Development Projects Group, 1978-1980 (Box 139, Folder 1391)
    - New York Chamber of Commerce and Industry - House Committee, 1978-1989 (Box 140, Folder 1392)
    - New York Chamber of Commerce and Industry - "The Infinite City" [Promotional Film], 1978-1980 (Box 140, Folder 1393)
    - New York Chamber of Commerce and Industry - Public Works Committee, 1982-1989 (Box 140, Folder 1394)
    - New York City Basketball Hall of Fame, 1994 (Box 140, Folder 1395)
    - New York City Borough President's Office, 1980 (Box 140, Folder 1396)
      Borough of Manhattan
    - New York City Bridge Commission, 1989 (Box 140, Folder 1397)
    - New York City Charter Revisions, 1974-August 1976 (Box 140, Folder 1398)
    - New York City Charter Revisions, September-December 1976 (Box 140, Folder 1399)
    - New York City Charter Revisions, 1977-1988 (Box 140, Folder 1400)
    - New York City Charter Revision, 1989 (Box 141, Folder 1401)
    - New York City Council, 1991-1992 (Box 141, Folder 1402)
    - New York City Council - Environmental Protection Committee Hearings, 1991 (Box 141, Folder 1403)
    - New York City Council - Land Use Subcommittee, 1994 (Box 141, Folder 1404)
    - New York City Council on Economic Education, 1981-1987 (Box 141, Folder 1405)
    - New York City Council on Economic Education, 1988-1989 (Box 141, Folder 1406)
    - New York City Council on Economic Education, 1990-1995 (Box 142, Folder 1407)
    - New York City Districting Commission, 1990-1991 (Box 142, Folder 1408)
    - New York City Economic Development Corporation, 1992 (Box 142, Folder 1409)
    - New York City Mayor's Office - General, 1974-1990 (Box 142, Folder 1410)
      Mayors Beame, Koch, Dinkins
    - New York City Mayor's Office of Lower Manhattan Development, 1972-1988 (Box 142, Folder 1411)
    - New York City Parks and Recreation Department, 1989 (Box 142, Folder 1412)
      Includes Annual Report of 1988 (prepared December 1989).
    - New York City Partnership, 1979-1983 (Box 142, Folder 1413)
    - New York City Partnership, 1984-1989 (Box 143, Folder 1414)
    - New York City Partnership, 1994 (Box 143, Folder 1415)
    - New York City Partnership - Information Technology Center, 1994 (Box 143, Folder 1416)
    - New York City Planning Commission - Lower Manhattan Plan, 1964-July 1965 (Box 143, Folder 1417)
    - New York City Planning Commission - Lower Manhattan Plan, August-December 1965 (Box 143, Folder 1418)
    - New York City Planning Commission - Lower Manhattan Plan, 1966-1968 (Box 143, Folder 1419)
      Includes a summary of the report, various correspondence, clippings, work outline, contracts for services to prepare the plan, etc.
      See Series 2.5 for additional copies of related reports.
    - New York City Planning Commission, 1979, 1986-1992 (Box 143, Folder 1420)
    - New York City Department of Ports and Terminals, 1982 (Box 143, Folder 1421)
    - New York City Public Development Corporation, 1981-1991 (Box 143, Folder 1422)
    - New York City Department of Sanitation, 1984-1990 (Box 144, Folder 1423)
    - New York City Seal - "BLC to have framed" (Box 144, Folder 1424)
      BLC refers to Barbara L. Christen.
    - New York City Sports Commission - Grand Prix, July 1991, 1990-1991 (Box 144, Folder 1425)
    - New York City Sports Commission, 1991-1994 (Box 144, Folder 1426)
      Goodwil Games; New York City Grand Prix, 1992; National Hockey League (NHL) All-Star Game, 1994.
    - New York City Department of Telecommunications and Energy, 1991 (Box 144, Folder 1427)
    - New York City Department of Transportation, 1989-1993 (Box 144, Folder 1428)
    - New York Convention and Visitor's Bureau, Inc., 1977-1992 (Box 144, Folder 1429)
    - New York Herald Tribune Fresh Air Fund Tour - Downtown Manhattan, May 20, 1961 (Box 144, Folder 1430)
    - New York Infirmary/Beekman Downtown Hospital, 1975-1989 (Box 144, Folder 1431)
    - New York Infirmary/Beekman Downtown Hospital, January-August 1990 (Box 145, Folder 1432)
    - New York Infirmary/Beekman Downtown Hospital, September 1990 (Box 145, Folder 1433)
    - New York Infirmary/Beekman Downtown Hospital, September 1990 (Box 145, Folder 1434)
    - New York Infirmary/Beekman Downtown Hospital, October-November 1990 (Box 145, Folder 1435)
    - New York Infirmary/Beekman Downtown Hospital, January-March 1991 (Box 145, Folder 1436)
    - New York Infirmary/Beekman Downtown Hospital, April 1991 (Box 146, Folder 1437)
    - New York Infirmary/Beekman Downtown Hospital, May-June 1991 (Box 146, Folder 1438)
    - New York Infirmary/Beekman Downtown Hospital, September-December 1991 (Box 146, Folder 1439)
    - New York Infirmary/Beekman Downtown Hospital - New York Downtown Hospital, 1992-1993 (Box 146, Folder 1440)
    - New York Infirmary/Beekman Downtown Hospital - New York Downtown Hospital, 1994-1995 (Box 146, Folder 1441)
    - New York Leadership Conference - Strengthening Tomorrow's Economy, November 5, 1987 (Box 147, Folder 1442)
    - New York Marriott Financial Center Hotel, 1993 (Box 147, Folder 1443)
    - New York Public Library - Downtown Branch, 1987 (Box 147, Folder 1444)
    - New York Public Library - Downtown Branch, 1988 (Box 147, Folder 1445)
    - New York Public Library - Downtown Branch, 1989-1990 (Box 147, Folder 1446)
      First ever Downtown Branch opened in 1989 at 9 Murray Street.
    - New York Society of Association Executives, 1989-1991 (Box 147, Folder 1447)
    - New York State Senate, 1989 (Box 147, Folder 1448)
    - New York State Urban Council, 1990 (Box 147, Folder 1449)
    - New York State Urban Council, 1991 (Box 147, Folder 1450)
    - New York State Urban Council, 1992-1994 (Box 147, Folder 1451)
    - New York Stock Exchange, 1961-1962 (Box 148, Folder 1452)
      RAC Photograph Collection, Series 1081, Box 2, Folder 58.
    - New York Stock Exchange, January-June 1963 (Box 148, Folder 1453)
    - New York Stock Exchange, August-December 1963 (Box 148, Folder 1454)
    - New York Stock Exchange, 1964-1965 (Box 148, Folder 1455)
    - New York Stock Exchange, January-March 1966 (Box 148, Folder 1456)
    - New York Stock Exchange - Transfer Tax, March 24, 1966 (Box 148, Folder 1457)
    - New York Stock Exchange, April-December 1966 (Box 148, Folder 1458)
    - New York Stock Exchange, 1967-1968 (Box 149, Folder 1459)
      RAC Photograph Collection, Series 1081, Box 3, Folder 59.
    - New York Stock Exchange, 1969-1973 (Box 149, Folder 1460)
    - New York Stock Exchange, 1975-1985 (Box 149, Folder 1461)
    - New York University, 1976-1992 (Box 149, Folder 1462)
    - Office Procedures, 1990-1992 (Box 149, Folder 1463)
    - Olympia and York (Stories, etc.), 1992 (Box 149, Folder 1464)
      Newspaper clippings dealing with Olympia and York Developments, Ltd.
    - Olympic Parade, August 15, 1984 (Box 149, Folder 1465)
    - Olympics '92, 1990-1991 (Box 149, Folder 1466)
    - Operation Interlock, 1974-1984 (Box 149, Folder 1467)
    - "Operation - Neat As A Pin", 1972-1978 (Box 150, Folder 1468)
      Includes: street map - litter basket survey.
    - Operation Safety Net - General, 1984 (Box 150, Folder 1469)
    - Operation Safety Net - General, 1985 (Box 150, Folder 1470)
    - Operation Safety Net - General, 1986-1989 (Box 150, Folder 1471)
    - Operation Safety Net - Letters of Intent, 1984-1985 (Box 150, Folder 1472)
    - Operation Safety Net - Letters of Intent, 1986-1987 (Box 150, Folder 1473)
    - "Operation Welcome Home" - Persian Gulf War, Flag Day, June 1991 (Box 151, Folder 1474)
    - Overall Economic Development Planning (OEDP) Committee and Report, 1986-1991 (Box 151, Folder 1475)
    - Pace College, 1961-1962 (Box 151, Folder 1476)
      Includes 4 copies of the program for the Inauguration of Edward Joseph Mortola as President of Pace College, January 19, 1961.
    - Pace College [Pace University], 1976-1986 (Box 151, Folder 1477)
    - Pace University, 1987-1992 (Box 151, Folder 1478)
    - Parades - Parade for the Yankees, April 10, 1961 (Box 151, Folder 1479)
    - Parades - President of the Tunisian Republic (His Excellency Habib Bourguiba), May 11, 1961 (Box 151, Folder 1480)
    - Parades - President of Pakistan, July 14, 1961 (Box 151, Folder 1481)
    - Parades - President of the Republic of Peru (Dr. Manual Prado), September 22, 1961 (Box 151, Folder 1482)
    - Parades - President for the Republic of Sudan, October 13, 1961 (Box 151, Folder 1483)
    - Parades - "Constellation", October 27, 1961 (Box 151, Folder 1484)
    - Parades, 1969-1990 (Box 151, Folder 1485)
    - Paris/Grands Projects, 1979-1989 (Box 152, Folder 1486)
    - Parking, 1970-1976 (Box 152, Folder 1487)
    - Parking Ban - Midtown and Downtown, 1962-1969 (Box 152, Folder 1488)
      Includes: architectural drawing of 5 story public parking garage, 23-25 Park Row, New York City, June 20, 1967.
    - Parking Ban - Midtown and Downtown, 1970-1973 (Box 152, Folder 1489)
    - Parks, 1971-1991 (Box 152, Folder 1490)
    - The Parks Council, December 1987 (Box 152, Folder 1491)
      Hudson River Esplanade Park: A Design Concept for the West Side Waterfront.
    - Peddlers, 1968-1969 (Box 152, Folder 1492)
      Includes: street map - peddler survey, October 9, 1968.
      7 photos attached to September 6, 1968 correspondence removed. See RAC Photograph Collection, Series 1081, Box 3, Folder 60.
    - Peddlers, 1970-1971 (Box 153, Folder 1493)
    - Peddlers - Photos, July 12 and 29, 1971 (Box 153, Folder 1494)
    - Peddlers, 1972 (Box 153, Folder 1495)
    - Peddlers, 1973-1977 (Box 153, Folder 1496)
    - Peddlers, 1978 (Box 153, Folder 1497)
    - Peddlers, 1979 (Box 153, Folder 1498)
      Contains: Cross and Brown & Company Downtown Office Building Map, copyright 1978. Oversized.
    - Peddlers, 1980-1981 (Box 153, Folder 1499)
    - Peddlers, 1982 (Box 154, Folder 1500)
    - Peddlers, 1983-1984 (Box 154, Folder 1501)
    - Peddlers, 1985-1989 (Box 154, Folder 1502)
    - Peddlers, 1990-1991 (Box 154, Folder 1503)
    - Peddlers, 1992-1994 (Box 154, Folder 1504)
      RAC Photograph Collection, Series 1081, Box 3, Folder 61.
    - Pedestrian, 1994 (Box 154, Folder 1505)
    - PediCabs, 1994 (Box 154, Folder 1506)
      Includes 16 color photocopies.
    - People Mover, 1971 (Box 154, Folder 1507)
    - People Mover, 1972 (Box 154, Folder 1508)
    - People Mover, 1973-1979 (Box 155, Folder 1509)
    - Personnel, Banking, etc., 1983-1988 (Box 155, Folder 1510)
    - Personnel - People File, 1989-1994 (Box 155, Folder 1511)
      Biographies, newspaper clippings, etc.
    - Personnel - Applicants, 1992-1994 (Box 155, Folder 1512)
    - Pier A, 1973-1995 (Box 155, Folder 1513)
      At Battery Park, New York City.
    - Plaque - Federal Hall - Wall Street, October 10, 1961, 1961-1970 (Box 155, Folder 1514)
      Photos and negatives removed. See RAC Photograph Collection, Series 1081, Box 3, Folder 62.
    - Poets House, 1992-1993 (Box 156, Folder 1515)
    - "Point of View" Synopisis (Box 156, Folder 1516)
    - Polytechnic Institute of New York, 1977 (Box 156, Folder 1517)
    - Port of New York Authority, 1960-1963 (Box 156, Folder 1518)
    - Port of New York Authority, 1964-1966 (Box 156, Folder 1519)
      Four photos of PATH trains(accompanying press release of October 22, 1964) removed. See RAC Photograph Collection, Series 1081, Box 3, Folder 63.
    - Port of New York Authority, 1967 (Box 156, Folder 1520)
    - Port of New York Authority, 1968-1972 (Box 156, Folder 1521)
      Architectural model of PATH Journal Square Transportation Center in Jersey City, New Jersey, 1968, corners damaged.
      RAC Photograph Collection, Series 1081, Box 3, Folder 64.
    - Port Authority of New York and New Jersey, 1973-1975 (Box 157, Folder 1522)
    - Port Authority of New York and New Jersey, 1976 (Box 157, Folder 1523)
    - Port Authority of New York and New Jersey, 1977 (Box 157, Folder 1524)
      Includes press release of May 18, 1977 announcing Roger H. Gilman has been named "Metropolitan Civil Engineer of the Year." Gilman was Acting Executive Director of The Port Authority of New York and New Jersey.
      Portrait of Roger H. Gilman removed. See RAC Photograph Collection, Series 1081, Box 3, Folder 65.
    - PATH - Port Authority Trans-Hudson, 1965-1979 (Box 157, Folder 1525)
      RAC Photograph Collection, Series 1081, Box 3, Folder 66.
    - Port Authority of New York and New Jersey, 1978-February 1979 (Box 157, Folder 1526)
    - Port Authority of New York and New Jersey, March-December 1979 (Box 157, Folder 1527)
    - Port Authority of New York and New Jersey, 1980 (Box 158, Folder 1528)
    - "The Port Authority of New York and New Jersey and the 1962 PATH - World Trade Center Project." Abraham Stein, copyright 1980. (Box 158, Folder 1529)
      A dissertation presented to the Faculty of the Graduate School of Business Administration, New York University, in partial fulfillment of the requirements for the degree of Doctor of Philosophy. This dissertation is a case study of the Port Authority, its rapid rail transit system known as PATH and the World Trade Center project, focusing on policy formulation and implementation.
    - Port Authority of New York and New Jersey, 1981 (Box 158, Folder 1530)
      Annual Reports are often housed in the folder of the following year. For example, the 1980 Annual Report was published in mid-1981, so it is housed in the 1981 folder.
    - Port Authority of New York and New Jersey, 1982 (Box 159, Folder 1531)
    - Port Authority of New York and New Jersey, January-June 1983 (Box 159, Folder 1532)
    - Port Authority of New York and New Jersey, July-December 1983 (Box 159, Folder 1533)
    - Port Authority of New York and New Jersey, January-August 1984 (Box 159, Folder 1534)
    - Port Authority of New York and New Jersey, September-December 1984 (Box 159, Folder 1535)
    - Port Authority of New York and New Jersey, January-June 1985 (Box 159, Folder 1536)
    - Port Authority of New York and New Jersey, July 1985 (Box 160, Folder 1537)
    - Port Authority of New York and New Jersey, August-December 1985 (Box 160, Folder 1538)
    - Port Authority of New York and New Jersey, 1986 (Box 160, Folder 1539)
    - Port Authority of New York and New Jersey, February-June 1987 (Box 160, Folder 1540)
    - Port Authority of New York and New Jersey, July-December 1987 (Box 160, Folder 1541)
    - Port Authority of New York and New Jersey, January-March 1988 (Box 160, Folder 1542)
    - Port Authority of New York and New Jersey, April-December 1988 (Box 161, Folder 1543)
    - Port Authority of New York and New Jersey, February-March 1989 (Box 161, Folder 1544)
    - Port Authority of New York and New Jersey, April-December 1989 (Box 161, Folder 1545)
    - Port Authority of New York and New Jersey, 1990 (Box 161, Folder 1546)
    - Port Authority of New York and New Jersey, 1991-1992 (Box 161, Folder 1547)
    - Port Promotion, 1983-1987 (Box 161, Folder 1548)
      New York-New Jersey Port Promotion Association.
    - Project Archive, 1991 (Box 161, Folder 1549)
    - Project Recommendations - Projects Now Under Way and in the Planning Stage, 1968 (Box 161, Folder 1550)
    - Project Recommendations - Major Recommendations and Accomplishments of the D-LMA, Inc., 1968 (Box 161, Folder 1551)
    - (New) Promotion Group for Downtown, 1985 (Box 162, Folder 1552)
    - Promotion of Downtown Committee (D-LMA), 1990 (Box 162, Folder 1553)
    - Public Spaces Project, 1976-1990 (Box 162, Folder 1554)
      Project For Public Spaces, Inc.
    - Real Estate - Rentals, Vacancies, Statistics, etc., 1974-1991 (Box 162, Folder 1555)
    - Real Estate Board of New York, Inc., 1980-1982 (Box 162, Folder 1556)
    - Real Estate Board of New York, Inc., 1983-1985 (Box 162, Folder 1557)
    - Real Estate Board of New York, Inc., 1986-1991 (Box 163, Folder 1558)
    - Real Estate Board of New York, Inc., 1992-1993 (Box 163, Folder 1559)
    - Real Estate Forum, 1961-1979 (Box 163, Folder 1560)
    - Redevelopment Plans - Release to City Officials, October 14, 1958 (Box 163, Folder 1561)
    - Regional Mobility Conference, December 13, 1988 (Box 163, Folder 1562)
      Various papers prepared for the Conference.
    - Regional Plan Association, 1979-1982 (Box 163, Folder 1563)
    - Regional Plan Association, 1983-1985 (Box 163, Folder 1564)
    - Regional Plan Association, 1986-1995 (Box 163, Folder 1565)
    - Rent Control, 1976-1987 (Box 164, Folder 1566)
    - Rikers Island, 1979 (Box 164, Folder 1567)
      Proposal - 5-year phased transfer of Rikers Island from New York City to New York State.
    - River Walk (East River Drive and 20th Street), 1989-1990 (Box 164, Folder 1568)
    - Route 9A (from Battery Place to 55th Street), 1993-1994 (Box 164, Folder 1569)
      Reconstruction project.
    - Royal Bank of Canada (Building), 1991 (Box 164, Folder 1570)
      Includes: architectural drawings.
    - Rudin Management Company, 1976 (Box 164, Folder 1571)
    - Runway New York Magazine, 1990 (Box 164, Folder 1572)
    - Safe Buildings Alliance, 1992-1993 (Box 164, Folder 1573)
    - Salomon Brothers, Inc., 1992 (Box 164, Folder 1574)
      Newspaper clippings.
    - Sanitation - New York City - General and Downtown, 1978-1982 (Box 164, Folder 1575)
    - Sanitation - New York City - General and Downtown, 1983-1985 (Box 164, Folder 1576)
    - Satellite Academy [for Career Education], 1975 (Box 165, Folder 1577)
    - Satellite Learning Center, 1990 (Box 165, Folder 1578)
    - School for the Physical City, 1992 (Box 165, Folder 1579)
    - The Seamen's Bank for Savings - History (Box 165, Folder 1580)
      30 Wall Street
    - The Seamen's Church Institute, 1965-1982 (Box 165, Folder 1581)
    - The Seamen's Church Institute, 1983-1984 (Box 165, Folder 1582)
    - The Seamen's Church Institute, 1985-1992 (Box 165, Folder 1583)
    - STOL Ports, 1966-1970 (Box 165, Folder 1584)
      STOL stands for Short Take-Off and Landing.
    - STOL Ports, 1971 (Box 166, Folder 1585)
    - STOL Ports, 1972-1973 (Box 166, Folder 1586)
    - Silverstein Properties, 1981-1982 (Box 166, Folder 1587)
    - Slide Presentations [D-LMA], 1965-1974 (Box 166, Folder 1588)
    - Small Business Administration, 1987 (Box 166, Folder 1589)
    - Smoking, 1986 (Box 166, Folder 1590)
    - Southbridge Towers, 1972-1975 (Box 166, Folder 1591)
    - South Ferry Projects, 1975-1979 (Box 166, Folder 1592)
    - South Ferry Projects, 1984-1987 (Box 166, Folder 1593)
    - South Street Seaport, 1966 (Box 167, Folder 1594)
    - South Street Seaport, 1967 (Box 167, Folder 1595)
    - South Street Seaport, 1968 (Box 167, Folder 1596)
      Includes: architectural drawing.
    - South Street Seaport, 1969-1970 (Box 167, Folder 1597)
    - South Street Seaport, 1971 (Box 167, Folder 1598)
    - South Street Seaport, 1972 (Box 167, Folder 1599)
    - South Street Seaport, 1973 (Box 168, Folder 1600)
      Photo of American Waterways Wind Orchestra Concert removed. See RAC Photograph Collection, Series 1081, Box 3, Folder 67.
    - South Street Seaport, 1974 (Box 168, Folder 1601)
      Includes: Architectural drawing of Fulton Ferry Landing; dated June 18, 1974.
    - South Street Seaport, 1975-1976 (Box 168, Folder 1602)
    - South Street Seaport, 1977 (Box 168, Folder 1603)
    - South Street Seaport, January-May 1978 (Box 168, Folder 1604)
      Front Street Development Plan, prepared by the South Street Seaport Corporation. Architect Benjamin Thompson and Associates.
    - South Street Seaport, June-December 1978 (Box 168, Folder 1605)
    - South Street Seaport, January-August 1979 (Box 169, Folder 1606)
    - South Street Seaport, September-December 1979 (Box 169, Folder 1607)
    - South Street Seaport, March-May 1980 (Box 169, Folder 1608)
    - South Street Seaport, June-July 1980 (Box 169, Folder 1609)
    - South Street Seaport, August-December 1980 (Box 169, Folder 1610)
    - South Street Seaport, January-June 1981 (Box 170, Folder 1611)
      "Seaport" and other publications of the South Street Seaport Museum, 1981.
    - South Street Seaport, July-October 1981 (Box 170, Folder 1612)
    - South Street Seaport, November 1981-1982 (Box 170, Folder 1613)
    - South Street Seaport, 1983-1984 (Box 170, Folder 1614)
    - South Street Seaport, 1985 (Box 170, Folder 1615)
    - South Street Seaport, 1986 (Box 170, Folder 1616)
    - South Street Seaport, 1987 (Box 171, Folder 1617)
    - South Street Seaport, 1988-1989 (Box 171, Folder 1618)
    - South Street Seaport, 1990-1991, 1994 (Box 171, Folder 1619)
    - Staggered Work Hours, 1958-1963 (Box 171, Folder 1620)
    - Staggered Work Hours - Survey, 1968-1970 (Box 171, Folder 1621)
    - Staggered Work Hours - Survey - Questionnaire (A-G), 1969 (Box 171, Folder 1622)
    - Staggered Work Hours - Survey - Questionnaire (H-W), 1969 (Box 171, Folder 1623)
    - Staggered Work Hours, 1970 (Box 172, Folder 1624)
    - Staggered Work Hours, February 1971 (Box 172, Folder 1625)
    - Staggered Work Hours, March-September 1971 (Box 172, Folder 1626)
    - Staggered Work Hours, January-March 1972 (Box 172, Folder 1627)
    - Staggered Work Hours, April 1972 (Box 172, Folder 1628)
    - Staggered Work Hours, May-December 1972 (Box 172, Folder 1629)
    - Staggered Work Hours, January-March 1973 (Box 173, Folder 1630)
    - Staggered Work Hours, April 1973 (Box 173, Folder 1631)
    - Staggered Work Hours, May 1973-1974 (Box 173, Folder 1632)
    - Staggered Work Hours, 1975 (Box 174, Folder 1633)
    - Staggered Work Hours, 1976 (Box 174, Folder 1634)
    - Staggered Work Hours, 1977 (Box 174, Folder 1635)
      RAC Photograph Collection, Series 1081, Box 3, Folder 68.
    - Staggered Work Hours, 1978-1980, 1991 (Box 174, Folder 1636)
    - Staggered Work Hours - Variable Work Hours Conference, Boston, Massachusetts, June 21, 1978 (Box 174, Folder 1637)
      Justin J. Murphy gave keynote address.
    - State University of New York (SUNY), 1984 (Box 174, Folder 1638)
    - Staten Island (New York), 1985-1987 (Box 174, Folder 1639)
    - Staten Island Ferry, 1980 (Box 174, Folder 1640)
    - Statistics Project, 1990 (Box 174, Folder 1641)
    - Statistics Project, 1991 (Box 174, Folder 1642)
      Summer project to develop a compilation of statistics and facts about Lower Manhattan for the D-LMA.
    - Statistics Project, 1991 (Box 174, Folder 1642A)
    - Street Closings - Flower Show and Music, May 24, 1971 (Box 175, Folder 1643)
    - Street Lighting, 1967-1972 (Box 175, Folder 1644)
    - Street Lighting, January-June 1973 (Box 175, Folder 1645)
    - Street Lighting, July 1973-1975, 1978 (Box 175, Folder 1646)
    - Street Lighting Fund - Accounting, 1973-1975 (Box 175, Folder 1647)
    - Stuyvesant High School, 1991 (Box 175, Folder 1648)
    - Subways, 1983 (Box 175, Folder 1649)
      Metropolitan Transit Authority (MTA) - Culture Stations Project
    - Subways - Second Avenue Subway - Statement of Edward F. Wagner [President - DLMA, Inc.] Before the Board of Estimate, August 12, 1968 (Box 175, Folder 1650)
    - Summer Jobs, 1984-1986 (Box 176, Folder 1651)